Wolf, Benjamin H. Additional Arbitration Files 5539
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 81-25 New City Sportswear vs. International Ladies Garment Workers Union, Local 140, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  11/27/81. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Insubordination; Improper Job Attitude
- 81-26 GTE Sylvania Wiring Devices, Incorporated vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), Local 398, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  7/14/81. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreement, Exhibits. Issue: Reinstatement--Following Illness
- 81-27 Atlantic Metal Hose Company vs. Local 455, International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers (IABSOIW), 1981 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  8/6/81. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Tardiness; Insubordination; Threats
- 81-28 New York State Office of Mental Health vs. Public Employee Federation, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  9/2/81. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Demotion--Absences, excessive; Tardiness
- 81-29 New City Sportswear vs. International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU), Local 140, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  5/81. Routine Correspondence, Agreements. Settled
- 81-30 City of New York vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  1/26/82. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Promotion--Testing of Employees
- 81-31 Editing Concepts vs. Local 177, International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees (IATSE), 1981 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  8/81. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 81-32 New York State Office of Mental Retardation vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1981 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- 81-33 Levin Fixture Corporation vs. United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 2682, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  7/81. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 81-34 Rutgers State University vs. Rutgers, Council of American Association of University Professors (AAUP) Chapters, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  9/81. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 81-35 Oak Beverages Incorporated vs. Local 812, International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1981 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  7/30/81. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Added Duties--Contract Interpretation
- 81-36 State of New York Office of Mental Retardation vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1981 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  7/23/81. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Insubordination; Improper Personal Conduct--Assault
- 81-37 Concord Hotel vs. Hotel Workers, Local 76, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  7/27/81. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Theft-- Intent.
- 81-38 Mobil Oil Corporation vs. Petroleum Trade Employees, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  6/81. Routine Correspondence. Settled.
- 81-39 Griffin Pipe Products vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2040, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  8/10/81. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Discharge--Plant Rules--Use of Telephone.
- 81-40 State of New Jersey, Trenton State College vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  12/17/81. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, TR. Issue: Union Elections--Election Procedures.
- 81-41 Waterview Nursing Home vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, Local 1199, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  10/81. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 81-42 Wappingers Central School District vs. Wappingers Federation of Transit, Custodial, and Maintenance Workers, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  11/5/81. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Agreements. Issue: Contract Interpretation--Workweek--Starting Time Change; Rates of Pay--Temporary Employees.
- 81-43 Weston Instruments Incorporated vs. Weston Employees Union, Incorporated, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  10/81. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 81-44 Mineola Union Free School District vs. Mineola Teachers' Association, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  6/81. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 81-45 U.S. Post Office vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  6/81. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled.
- 81-46 U.S. Post Office vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- 81-47 New York State, Canton State University vs. American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Council 82, Security Unit Employees, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  11/2/81. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Vacations--Scheduling.
- 81-48 Star Expansion Industries Corporation vs. Local 445, International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 1981 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  8/20/81. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Discharge--Absences, Unauthorized.
- 81-49 American Tack and Hardware Company vs. Service Employees International Union, Local 1-J, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  8/17/81. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Discharge--Theft.
- 81-50 Barnert Memorial Hospital vs. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees Local 1199-J, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 27)
- 81-51 State of New York Office of Mental Retardation vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1982 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  2/5/82. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Schedules of Work--Change in Schedule
- 81-52 Trans World Airlines vs. Lorny Pate, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  11/16/81. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Discharge--Theft--Unauthorized Taking of Property
- 81-53 Kay Fries Incorporated vs. International Chemical Workers Union, Local 677, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  8/28/81. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Overtime--Call-In--Rates of Pay.
- 81-54 St. Patrick's Home For The Aged vs. Service Employees International Union, Local 144, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  9/81. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 81-55 State of New Jersey, William Paterson College vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  10/27/81. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Promotion--Probationary Employee--Failure To Qualify
- 81-56 New Jersey State, William Paterson College vs. Council of New Jersey State College Locals, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- 81-57 State of New York Unified Court System vs. Court Officers' Benevolent Association of Nassau County, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  9/81. Routine Correspondence, Supporting Documents. Cancelled
- 81-58 United Parcel Service vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 177, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- 81-59 U.S. Bronze Powders Incorporated vs. International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE), Local 427, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  11/12/81. Routine Correspondence, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Vacancies--Method of Filling--Posting.
- 81-60 New York City Banking vs. ?, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- 81-61 Georgia Pacific Corporation vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Local 1920, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  11/27/81. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Supporting Documents, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Elimination of Jobs--Technological Displacement Allowance
- 81-62 New York Yacht Club vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees International Union, Local 6, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  10/5/81. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Promotion--Seniority; Hiring--Hiring Halls
- 81-63 Flower Hospital vs. United Salaried Physicians and Dentists, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  6/10/82. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Seniority
- 81-64 Connecticut Light and Power vs. Local 457, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), 1982 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  2/12/82. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Vacancies--Seniority--Contract Interpretation
- 81-65 Nassau County Police Department vs. Policemen's Benevolent Association, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  11/30/81. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Agreements. Issue: Transfers--Change In Assignment.
- 81-66 E.I. DuPont de Nemours and Company vs. Newark Plant Employees Union, Local 18, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  3/5/82. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Supporting Documents, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Fights and Altercations.
- 81-67 New York State Office of Mental Retardation vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1981 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- 81-68 New York State Office of Mental Retardation vs. Civil Service Employees Association, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  10/16/81. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Suspension--Improper Personal Conduct--Assaults.
- 81-69 City of New York Department of Corrections vs. Correction's Officers' Benevolent Association, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  11/19/81. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Call-In--Overtime--Rates of Pay.
- 81-70 Concord Hotel vs. Local 76 Hotel Workers, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  11/9/81. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Discharge-- Theft.
- 81-71 State University of New York, Stoney Brook vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1981 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  11/81. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 81-71 New York State Office of Mental Retardation vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1981 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  11/23/81. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Suspension--Improper Personal Conduct--Assault
- 81-73 Ames Metal Molding Company vs. Local 365, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), 1981 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  12/81. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 82-1 Harte and Company Incorporated vs. International Leather Goods, Plastics, and Novelty Workers' Union, Joint Board, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  4/29/82. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Rates of Pay--Reduction.
- 82-8 Cummins Metropolitan vs. International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), District 15, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  3/82. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 82-3 State of New York Unified Court System vs. Court Officers Benevolent Association of Nassau County, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  1/28/83. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Vacation--Computation.
- 82-4 Watervliet Arsenal vs. National Association of Government Employees, Local R2-98, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  6/10/82. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Contract Interpretation.
- 82-5 Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority vs. Bridge and Tunnel Officers' Benevolent Association, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  2/83. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn
- 82-6 Somerset Bus Company vs. Amalgamated Transit Union Division, 1478, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  6/1/82. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Supporting Documents. Issue: Discharge--Absences, excessive.
- 82-7 Teneco Chemicals, Incorporated vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 679, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  6/1/82. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Layoff--Seniority
- 82-8 State of New Jersey, Division of State Police vs. State Troopers Fraternal Association, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  4/22/82. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Transcripts, Agreement, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Union Representatives and Business--Time Off for Union Business
- 82-9 State of New York Division for Youth vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1982 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  5/17/82. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discipline--Negligence and Carelessness
- 82-10 GAF Corporation vs. United Cement, Lime, and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 490, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  2/82. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 82-11 GAF Corporation vs. United Cement, Lime, and Gypsum Workers International Union, Local 490, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- 82-12 Classic Truck Rental Corporation vs. International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), Local 138, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  4/82. Routine Correspondence. Settled
- 82-13 U.S. Postal Service vs. American Postal Workers Union, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  11/82. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- 82-14 U.S. Postal Service vs. National Association of Letter Carriers, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  6/82. Routine Correspondence. Cancelled
- 82-15 Griffin Pipe Products Company vs. United Steelworkers of America, Local 2040, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  6/21/82. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, TR. Issue: Discharge--Plant Rules--Drinking
- 82-16 State of New York Letchworth Village Developmental Center vs. Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), 1982 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  5/24/82. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Improper Personal Conduct--Drinking
- 82-17 Delta Upholsterers Incorporated vs. Upholsterers, Decorators and Allied Crafts Union, Local 44, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  5/10/82. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Discharge--Absences, excessive; Tardiness; Improper Job Attitude--General Attitude.
- 82-18 U.S. Defense Contract Administration Services Region-New York vs. American Federation of Government Employees, Local 2567, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  10/9/82. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, Supporting Documents. Issue: Promotion--Eligibility
- 82-19 State of New York Office of Mental Retardation vs. Public Employees Federation, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  7/7/82. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Improper Personal Conduct--Assault.
- 82-20 Elizabethtown Gas Company vs. Utility Workers of America, Local 424, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  1/18/83. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Change In Procedure; Standards of Production--Workload
- Series II - Miscellaneous Case Files (Box 39)
- Alatex Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  10/30/72. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Discharge--Theft
- Alatex Incorporated vs. Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, Local 910, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  9/21/72. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Union Security--Check-Off.
- American Airlines (System Board of Adjustment, Division II) vs. Transport Workers Union, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  3/24/72. M-250-69. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Timeliness--Grievance; Rates of Pay
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  10/13/72. M-5-70. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Classification of Job--Rates of Pay
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  2/13/73. M-243-71. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Overtime-- Rates of Pay.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  2/13/73. M-245-72. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Contracting Out--Bargaining Unit Work
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  3/13/73. M-12-R. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Contracting Out--Bargaining Unit Work
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  3/13/73. M-480-71. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Jobs-- Assignment To Work Outside Classification.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  3/13/73. S-104-71. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Seniority--Rates of Pay
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  6/27/73. M-386-70. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Classification of Jobs--Demotion
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  4/23/73. M-639-72. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Demotion; Seniority; Timeliness
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  4/23/73. M-672-72. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Layoff--Seniority-- Bumping.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  5/7/73. M-159-69. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Seniority.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  5/14/73. M-232-72. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Supporting Documents. Issue: Call-In--Seniority.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  6/19/73. M-187-71. Transcripts, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Jobs-- Classification of Jobs
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  6/21/73. M-197-73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits, TR. Issue: Overtime--Failure to Schedule.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  6/26/73. M-344-71. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  6/27/73. M-644-72. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Layoff- Seniority.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  6/26/73. M-643-72. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Assignment to Work Outside Classification--Rates of pay.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  6/28/73. M-469-71. Routine Correspondence, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Layoff-- Seniority.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  7/2/73. M-113-17. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Overtime
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  7/9/73. M-275-71. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Contracting Out-- Past Practice.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  8/21/73. M-187-71. Routine Correspondence. Withdrawn.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  9/4/73. M-355-72. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Contracting Out--Assignment of Jobs.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  10/3/73. M-392-72. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Layoff--Seniority.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  9/14/73. M-407-70. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Layoff--Lack of Work.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  9/17/73. M-277-72. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Contracting Out--Maintenance Work.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  9/21/73. M-200-72. Transcripts, Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Reinstatement--Recall-Availability.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  12/3/73. M-245,246-72. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Bargaining Unit Work.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  12/3/73. M-478-71. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Layoff--Seniority.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  12/18/73. M-395-72. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Layoff--Seniority.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  2/12/74. M-274-71. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Assignment of Job--Classification of Job--Standards of Production.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  3/27/74. M-647-72. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Contracting Out.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  4/1/74. M-504-73. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Recall-- Seniority.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  4/1/74. M-753-72. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Management Rights.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  4/3/74. M-414-73. Transcripts, Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Withdrawn.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  7/8/74. M-388-71. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Change in Procedure.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  7/8/74. M-182-72, 185-72. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, AM, Exhibits. Issue: Layoff- -Seniority.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  7/8/74. M-2013-74. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Exhibits, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Contracting Out--Bargaining Unify Work.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  7/9/74. M-105-73. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Training.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  9/3/74. M-641-73. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Contracting Out--Management Rights.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  9/3/74. M-289-73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Assignment of Jobs-- Assignment to Work Outside Classification.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  9/3/74 M-687-73. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, Transcripts, Exhibits. Issue: Shift Scheduling--Irregular Shift.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  9/10/74 M-314-73. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes. Issue: Contracting Out--Bargaining Unit Work.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  9/10/74. M-571-74. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Layoff--Remedy for Improper Layoff--Rates of Pay.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  9/10/74. S-50-74. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Contracting Out--Management Rights.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  9/13/74. M-1914-74. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Contracting Out--Bargaining Unit Work.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  9/27/74. M-1796. Routine Correspondence, Transcripts, Arbitrator's Notes, Exhibits. Issue: Layoff--Contracting Out.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  9/27/74. S-161-74. Routine Correspondence, Arbitrator's Notes, TR. Issue: Assignment of Jobs--Subcontracting--Management Rights.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers Union, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 19)